bizzduniya.com 2016-05-14

# Bizzduniya.com - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how BizzDuniya.com handle your personal information. We collect, use, & share personal information to help the BizzDuniya.com Online Portal ("BizzDuniya") work & to keep it safe (details below). In formal terms, BizzDuniya.com, acting itself and through its subsidiaries, is the "data controller" of your personal information. This policy is effective 01/01/2011

**Collection**  
Information posted on BizzDuniya is obviously publicly available. Our servers are located in Hyderabad, India. Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer & storage of that information on our servers. We collect and store the following personal information:

  * __Company Name, Contact Person Name, Address, Mobile No., Email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information.
  * __Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from BizzDuniya and Ad data (all through cookies – you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site).
  * __Other information, including users IP address and standard web log information.

**Use We use user's personal information to:**

  * __provide our services.
  * __resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems.
  * __encourage safe trading and enforce our policies.
  * __customize users' experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates.
  * __communicate marketing and promotional offers to you.
  * __Do other things for users as described when we collect the information.

**Disclosure**

  * __All information contained by BizzDuniya is treated as strictly confidential and BizzDuniya does not and will not disclose or share such confidential information to / with any external organization.
  * __The users' privacy is very important to us. We do not and shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent users' personal information to third parties without users' explicit consent.
  * __We may be required from time to time to disclose users' personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.
  * __BizzDuniya also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to fraud on account of such transactions during the period BizzDuniya retains such information.
  * __We may also disclose personal information to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protects anyone's rights, property or safety.
  * __We may also share personal information with:- Corporate affiliates who help detect or prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to). - Service providers who help with our business operations.

**Using Information from Bizzduniya**  
You may use personal information gathered from BizzDuniya only to follow up with another user about a his / her business, not to send spam/ phising or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.

**Access, Modification, and Deletion.**  
You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your business details or account status page. Contact customer support at to review any personal information we store that is not available on BizzDuniya. There may be a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent bad guys from coming back.

**Data Security**  
We use a number of mechanisms (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect the security and integrity of your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

**Confidentiality of Information**  
Users who use any of the features on BizzDuniya agrees and accepts that they have been fully informed by BizzDuniya.com that the use of features may lead to publication, to all users of BizzDuniya, of any personal information uploaded by them while using any specific feature on BizzDuniya.com. Users further agree that the authenticity of, and consequences from the uploading by users of any personal information of themselves or any other person, are the sole responsibility of the user. Users further agree and accept that the terms of the Privacy Policy will be applicable to the use of all features, existing and new. However, the Users agree and accept that confidentiality of information uploaded on such features has been waived by the Users of such features themselves.

**General**  
We may update, upgrade, modify (partially &/or fully) this policy at any time.. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to [info@bizzduniya.com](mailto:info@bizzduniya.com)
